http://www.troy.edu/privacy-statement.html

Privacy Statement
Toggle Sub-MenuAbout UsFind TROYDothan CampusMontgomery CampusPhenix City CampusTroy CampusTROY OnlineTROY Support CentersAccreditationCareer Ready and Prepared for LifeLeadershipMission and VisionOffices & DepartmentsPartnershipsRankings and Points of PrideStrategic ApproachStudent Achievement at Troy UniversityTobacco Free CampusFinancial DisclosureHistorical TimelineAcademicsAcademic CatalogsAccessibility StatementAccreditation StatementAlumniAlumniAlumni of the YearBenefitsBoard of DirectorsBoard Presidents (Past)ChaptersLifetime MembersStaffTROY License PlateApplications & AdmissionsAdmissions Process & RequirementsCheck Application StatusNet Price CalculatorNew Student OrientationUndergraduate & Graduate TestingVisit UsTrojan DayGroup ToursTROY Video TourA-Z SitemapCalendarCampusCommunity & OutreachACCESSALWACCenter for Public ServiceCIBEDCommunity OutreachConfucius InstituteContinuing EducationCorporate PartnershipsGovernment RelationsInternational Arts CenterResources on DeafnessRosa Parks Library & MuseumSmall Business Development CenterSponsored ProgramsTROY Public RadioTROY TrojanVisionW.A. Gayle PlanetariumWalking TrailsWiregrass ArchivesCampsMiss TROYContactePolicy000 - ePolicy Manual1000 - Miscellaneous100 - Policy200 - Governance300 - Academics400 - Students500 - Grants and Research600 - Human Resources700 - Finance800 - Technology900 - AdvancementFast TrackFind a LocationFuture StudentsGivingAnnual GivingMeet Our TeamSpecial Events & Special ProjectsTroy FoundationInternationalEnglish as a Second Language (ESL)International Student ServicesMeet the StaffStudent Services ScholarsStudy @ TROY outside the United StatesVisiting ScholarsCenter for International ProgramsLibrariesFoundationGrantsLibrary CatalogMilitary Service: A History in PostcardsPalladium ArchivesStaffWade Hall PostcardsWiregrass ArchivesMilitary & VeteransHomeAcademicsMilitary & Family ScholarshipSupport CentersTROY for TroopsTROY OnlineU.S. ArmyU.S. Coast GuardU.S. Marine CorpU.S. National GuardU.S. NavyVeteran BenefitsNet Price CalculatorNewsOnlineTROY OnlineAre you ready for Online Learning? Take the Quiz.Tour a Simulated Canvas CourseLearning Online FAQsTechnical RequirementsTools and SupportStudent Disability ServicesSchedule of ClassesStudent GuideParents & FamiliesPrivacy StatementRead Our DisclaimerStudent ComplaintsScholarships, Costs, & AidCosts
Financial Aid A-Z IndexFinancial AidScholarships Student Disability ServicesResources on Deafness & BlindnessStudent Life & ResourcesArts & CultureCampus MediaCampus RecreationDiningGroups & OrganizationsHousingStudent ResourcesTrojan CenterFree in 48TROY Live Broadcast
Privacy Statement
Troy University observes the applicable principles of the EU General Data Protection
Regulation. Visit our GDPR page for more information.
Troy University is committed to protecting your privacy. The University has established
this privacy policy and is providing it to you so that you can understand the manner
in which Troy University collects and uses your information and the efforts we use
to protect it. The University does not collect any personally identifiable information
about you unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.
By personal information, we mean information that can be used to identify or contact
an individual. Troy University does not actively share personal information about
website visitors. Personal information provided by visitors, such as email addresses
or information submitted via online forms, is used by the University to assist individual
visitors as necessary. This assistance may involve redirecting an inquiry or comment
to another University individual or unit better suited to provide resolution.
Our website makes use of various technologies to collect information about types and
versions of Internet browsers used when accessing our website. This information and
information about Internet IP addresses, as well as date and time web pages are visited,
are stored in various security and traffic logs. Our service provider reviews these
logs, using statistical analysis, in an effort to track and predict traffic patterns
and estimate resource needs. Unless we are tracking down a technical problem or we
suspect either fraudulent behavior or illegal conduct, we do not trace specific user
sessions. Because Troy University is a public institution, some information collected
from its website may be subject to the Alabama Open Records Act, or in some instances,
the University may be compelled by law to release information gathered from its web
servers. Some web servers at Troy University may adopt different privacy statements
as their specific needs require that may differ from this statement.
Troy University monitors anonymous website visitor traffic through the use of cookies
provided by third-party services, including Google Analytics, to review website performance
and to identify enhancements that may benefit visitors based on current navigation
patterns and search trends. The university may contract with third-party vendors to
show our advertisements on non-TROY websites and other digital delivery mechanisms.
No personally-identifiable information is stored and collected by the university for
these purposes.
Troy University also complies with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA),
which prohibits the release of educational records without student permission. For
more details on FERPA, currently enrolled students should consult the Troy University
Student Handbook (The Oracle) or the University’s Office of Academic Records and University
Registrar.
Questions about this privacy statement or practices of any Troy University website
should be directed to our Website Feedback Form.
©
